-嘿   -嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
我们来道别
We're here to say goodbye.
要去俄亥俄州
We're off to Ohio.
对哦  领养面谈
Oh, right, your adoption interview.
是啊  我们去见未来我们孩儿他妈
Yep. We'll meet the lady who could be carrying our baby.
难以置信  你们回来时
I can't believe it. When you come back,
会带着婴儿  太奇怪了
you'll have a baby. That is so weird.
也很不正确
And so incorrect.
她只怀孕几个月
She's only a couple months pregnant.
她选中了我们的申请表
She liked our application
是否喜欢我们还不一定
but might not like us.
她会喜欢你们的
Come on, she's gonna love you guys.
谢谢
Thank you.
但我们尽量不期望过高
But we're trying not to get our hopes up.
还有很多事情挡在我们面前
A lot could still get in our way.
她可能会决定拒绝把孩子给人领养
She could decide against adoption,
也可能选中其他夫妇
like another couple better.
你们打算给小孩取啥名字
What are you gonna name it?
我就有这个本事
I could develop a condition
费尽口舌
in which I talk and talk
而旁人却充耳不闻
and no one hears a word.
试想  如果一切顺利
But just think, okay? What if everything goes right?
如果她真选了你们俩呢
What if this woman does pick you guys?
天  那她就会选我们
Oh, my God. She's gonna pick us!
我们决心
So we're standing firm on
决不期望过高
"not getting our hopes up"?
我明白  有可能出差错
No. I know things could still go wrong,
但万一顺利
but if they don't...
如果没有问题
...if this works out,
我们就会有孩子了  孩子
we're gonna have a baby. A baby!
是的  但是...
Yes. But--
会成功的
Oh, my God. It's gonna work!
我们会成功的
We're gonna make it work!
我要当妈妈
I'm gonna be a mommy,
你要当爸爸
and you're gonna be a daddy!
回见了  你们这群笨蛋
All right, I'll see you suckers.
我要去领个娃娃了
I'm gonna go get me a baby!
管它呢  我要当爹啦
Screw it. I'm gonna be a daddy!
菲比跟谁在一起呢
Hey, who's Phoebe with?
我想说
I wanna say,
会跟我上床的姑娘
"Someone I'm gonna have sex with."
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你那朋友是谁啊
So who's your friend?
那是莎拉
Oh, that's Sarah.
不  你少打我朋友的主意
No. Don't you get any ideas.
我再也不给你
I'm not setting you up with
撮合我的朋友了
any more of my friends.
为什么  为什么
Why? Why?
因为你约一个睡一个
Because you'll date her once...
然后就把人家忘到九霄云外
...sleep with her, then forget she exists.
举例说明一下
Name one friend of yours I did that with.
-曼蒂  -曼蒂啊
- Mandy.  - Mandy, huh?
金发大胸辣妹
Really hot blond, big boobs?
错
No.
难怪我记不住她
Might be why I don't remember, huh?
你好象把我当别人了
Do you think I'm someone else?
过去我也许
Look, I may not have treated
待你朋友不好
your friends well in the past.
但我现在成熟多了
But I have grown up a lot.
真的  是吧  瑞秋
Really. Honest. Rach?
信不信由你  是真的
Yeah, believe it or not, it's true.
乔伊和我交往的时候很乖
I mean, when Joey and I were together...
非常好
...he was wonderful.
体贴成熟
He was thoughtful and mature.
我们交往那一周
And for the one week that we went out...
他都没和其他女人上床
...he didn't sleep with anybody else.
成长
Growth.
好  给你她的电话号码
Fine, I'll give you her number.
谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
我保证我不会忘记这个
And I promise you I will not forget this one.
-曼蒂  -莎拉
- Mandy.  - Sarah!
莎拉
Sarah.
-嘿   -嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
嗨
Hey.
嗨  给点着装建议
Hey, guys, I need some fashion advice.
帽子好看吗
How does this look?
有点...  有点低  戴高点
Well, it's-- It's a little low. Pick it up a little.
再高
A little bit more.
好了
There you go.
扔一边去
Now throw it away.
别这样  这帽子多好看
Come on! This looks good.
罗斯  相信我
Ross, please trust me.
我一个月买30本时尚杂志
I buy 30 fashion magazines a month.
我可能不清楚谁想竞选总统
Now I don't know who's running for president
或是北约那些人都是谁对谁
or who that NATO guy is...
但我知道
...but I do know that
你该离那帽子越远越妙
you have to get far away from that hat.
见鬼
Damn it. God....
明晚我要约会
I have this date tomorrow night,
我得扮帅才行
and I have to look cool.
如果你需要着装建议
If you need fashion help,
明天我和瑞秋要去购物
Rachel and l are going shopping tomorrow.
欢迎同去
You're more than welcome to come with us.
真的  太好了
Really? That would be great.
我必须有备而去
I mean, I have to do something.
她总是取笑我的衣着
She kind of teased me about how I dress.
能看出来  就你那衬衣
I can see why. Nice shirt.
你和我穿得一样啊
You're wearing the same shirt.
白痴"盖璞"  什么人都穿
Stupid Gap on every corner!
请随便坐
Make yourselves comfortable,
我带艾瑞卡过来
and I'll be back with Erica.
好  谢啦
Okay, thank you.
总算到了
Well, this is it.
你状态如何
Are you okay?
很好  对话会有点奇怪
Yeah, it's just weird, you know?
"我叫钱德勒
It's like, "Hi, I'm Chandler.
你体内的小人  可以给我养吗"
May I have the human growing inside you?"
你会表现出色的
You're gonna be great.
你也是
那显然
Well, obviously.
莫妮卡  钱德勒
Monica? Chandler?
这位是艾瑞卡
I'd like you to meet Erica.
嗨
Hi.
真高兴跟你见面
Hi. It is so, so nice to meet you.
-嗨   -谢谢你同意见我们
- Hi. - Thank you for agreeing to see us.
-嗨   -你们熟悉一下
- Hi.  - I'll let you get acquainted.
好的
Okay.
你们是莫妮卡  钱德勒
So it's Monica and Chandler?
你们的档案代号是"CRW33815-d号"
I only know you as "File CRW33815-D."
朋友们就这么叫我们
That's what our friends call us.
天啊  你们这一对太令人羡慕了
Gosh, you know, you're just such an amazing couple. It's...
都让人有点敬畏
...kind of intimidating.
你过奖了
I don't know about that.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
我是说  您是医生就够好了
I mean, it's enough that you're a doctor.
您竟然还娶了个牧师
But on top of it, you're married to a reverend?
这不是我们...
I don't think that's exactly--
让她说完  医生
Let her finish, doctor.
-嗨   -嗨
- Hey.  - Hey.
莎拉昨晚跟你一起很愉快
My friend Sarah had a great time last night.
是吗
Yeah.
是啊  这次你会再约她吗
Yeah, so you gonna call this one back?
绝不
No.
你说什么呢  莎拉很棒
What are you talking about? Sarah's great.
是吗  你知道你的很棒的朋友
Oh, really? You want to know
干了什么好事
what your "great" friend did?
我们出去吃饭
We're out to dinner, okay?
相处融洽
We were getting along,
聊得开心
having a really nice time.
我也觉得她很酷
I was thinking she was really cool.
然后  突然间...
And then, out of nowhere...
就这样
That's it?
这就是你不想再跟她约会的理由
That's why you won't go out with her again?
不就吃了你的薯条吗  有什么大不了
So she took some fries. Big deal.
我不是气她吃我几根薯条
Hey, look, it's not about a few fries.
你得清楚薯条的象征意义
It's about what the fries represent.
-啥  -所有食物
- What?  - All food!
对不起
Well, I'm sorry.
竟然介绍你
I can't believe I set you up
和这么个"怪物"约会
with such a monster!
我带女孩吃饭
Hey, look, I take a girl out...
她点什么都可以
...she can order whatever she wants.
越多越好
The more the better, all right?
但不可以自己
Just don't order
只点沙拉却夺我的食物
a garden salad and then eat my food!
这么做有可能被切手指的
That's a good way to lose some fingers.
谢天谢地你来了  你来评评理
Thank God you're here. Listen to this.
怎么了
What?
乔伊昨晚约我朋友
Joey and my friend are out last night,
在吃晚饭的时候
having dinner, and she reaches over...
-她伸手拿他的薯条  -哦  不
- ...and takes a few of his fries--  - Oh, no!
这有什么
What?
你知道这条规则
You know about the plate thing?
是是  乔伊从不分享食物
Oh, yeah, yeah. No, Joey doesn't share food.
上星期我们一起吃早餐
I mean, just last week we were having breakfast...
他盘里有些葡萄
...and he had a couple grapes on his plate.
你不让她吃葡萄
You wouldn't let her have a grape?
不  不是我
No, not me.
是艾玛
Emma.
乔伊从不分享食物
Joey doesn't share food!
我还是坚持认为就因为这件破事
Well, I still think that is a stupid reason
放弃她很不明智
not to call someone again.
你再约她  好吧
You are calling her, okay?
如果有必要
And if you need to,
干脆再点一盘薯条不就完了
then just get an extra plate of fries for the table.
这主意不错
I like that.
共享缓冲区
A sharing buffer. Yeah.
多点一盘薯条
Yeah, I'll order some extra fries.
再点一盘洋葱
Maybe a plate of onion rings.
好  好
Yeah. Yeah.
还要鸡尾虾
And a shrimp cocktail.
再要些辣鸡翅
And some Buffalo wings.
或许  一个披萨
Maybe.... Maybe an individual pizza, huh?
和炸干酪牛肉棒
And some mozzarella sticks.
我们在谈什么
What were we talking about?
这地方太好了
Wow, this place is awesome.
我们还是走吧
We should just go.
我在这淘不到什么的
I'm not gonna find anything here.
这的东西都太可笑了
This stuff is ridiculous.
这地方简直太赞了
Oh, this place is great!
瑞秋  我才不会穿这个
Rach, come on, I'm not gonna wear any of this.
我才不穿银色的
Nothing silver.
-为什么   -有毛毛的
- Why?  - Okay, nothing with hair.
更不穿带挂锁的
And nothing with padlocks on it!
罗斯  看看
Ross, look. Look,
我知道肯定能挑出几件的
I know that some of this stuff is out there.
但你看这  看看这个
But I mean, come on, look at this.
看看这件毛衣
Look at this sweater.
你看多好看
I mean, this is just beautiful.
是很柔软
Wow, this is really soft.
350元
350 dollars?
从700块打折下来
Down from 700.
你差不多省了200块呢
You're saving, like, 200 bucks.
今天逻辑学和数学
Both logic and math
都饱受摧残
are taking a serious hit today.
这件好  很衬你
Hey, check this out. It's totally you.
哇哦  这件看起来不错
Wow. Actually, this looks pretty good.
是啊
Yeah.
《男孩就是男孩》
"Boys will be boys"?
-本来就是   -好好
- What? They will be!  - All right.
算了  我走
That's it, I'm getting out of here.
别  罗斯  等等嘛
No, Ross, wait, come on.
还有其他的呢
There's other stuff here.
衬衣和裤子都不错
There's some nice shirts, these nice pants.
其实  这些看起来挺适合我
Actually, these might look pretty good on me.
嗯  是的  你知道你应该干嘛么
Yes, they will. You know what you should do?
你随便转转先
Go take a walk.
我知道你尺码,
All right? I know your size,
我帮你挑些上等货色
and I'll pick out some really good stuff for you.
-当真   -对
- Really?  - Yes.
我知道男人穿什么最性感
I know what looks sexy on guys.
穿我推荐的衣服
Just wear what I suggest,
不迷死她才怪
and she is gonna go nuts for you.
你是说...
So you're saying...
我若穿这条裤子
...if I wear these pants,
她会允许我侵犯
I might be getting into hers?
为什么男人老跟我来这套
Why do men keep talking to me like this?
我是医生
So the fact that I'm a doctor
我太太是牧师
and my wife's a reverend...
这对你很重要
...that's important to you?
是啊  很多申请人都很优秀
Yeah. I read some great applications...
但是我想
...but I thought,
带孩子谁能比得上牧师
"Who better than a minister to raise a child?"
阿门
Amen.
另外  我觉得把孩子交给个医生是很好的
Plus, I thought the baby would be in good hands with a doctor.
很好的一双手
Good hands.
疗伤圣手
Healing hands.
牧师  我能问一下
Reverend, can I ask?
圣经上对领养孩子怎么说吗
Does the Bible say anything about adoption?
但做无妨
It says, "Do it."
她让他们领养了一个婴孩
"And behold, she did adopt unto them a baby.
此乃善举
And it was good."
-哇  -是啊  我也哇
- Wow.  - Yeah, wow.
我在想  你们工作都责任重大
I was wondering-- You both have such serious jobs.
你有时间兼顾孩子和你的教友吗
Would you have time to take care of a baby and your flock?
我的教友  我的教友们没事儿
Oh, no, my flock? My flock is good.
这个时候  我的教友都是自己照顾自己
Yeah. My flock pretty much takes care of themselves by this point.
好教友  教友...
Good flock. Flock...
当医生很花时间吧
But being a doctor, that must take up a lot of time.
我的情况不同
Not for me it doesn't.
谈得如何
So how's everything going in here?
太棒了
We're great.
我想问题我都问完了
I think I may have asked all my questions.
很好  你们有什么要问她
Good. Do you have questions for Erica?
我想问问
Yeah, actually.
你读到满意的申请表
So you read a file that you liked...
然后告诉代理人编号
...and then you gave the agency the serial number
然后他们联系到我们
and they contacted us?
我们的系统中用户完全匿名
Yes. Our system ensures total anonymity.
我们以此为荣
We're very proud of it.
应该骄傲
You should be.
真的是一流
You're really on top of stuff.
别的没什么了
Well then, if there's nothing else,
那我们俩谈谈
then the two of us should talk.
实际上…
I actually....
-我想我们不必谈了 -为什么不
- I don't think we have to. - We don't?
我看了你们的档案
Yeah, when I read about you two,
就确定要选你们
I was pretty sure I wanted you...
但还想当面见见你们
...but I just thought we should meet face to face.
我决定了
I've made my decision.
就选他们
I choose them.
哦  天啊  太棒了
Oh, my God, this is great.
太棒了  听见吗
This is so great. Did you hear that?
是的  听见了
Yeah, I did.
嘿
Hey.
谢谢  太谢谢了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
你将来一定进天堂
You are so going to heaven!
我们买了些很棒的东西
We got some really great stuff.
对
Yeah.
但是  有些胸罩似乎不妥
Yeah, but I'm not sure about some of the bras I got.
真的  你能穿上试给我看吗
Really? Do you want to try some of them on for me?
好
Okay.
等一下  我们是在乔伊的幻想里吗
Wait, are we in Joey's imagination?
糟糕  错拿罗斯一袋
Oh, no. I took one of Ross' bags by mistake.
我那件不见了
And one of mine is missing.
肯定在罗斯那里
Ross probably has it.
找他拿回来好了
You'll get it from him later.
你觉得如何
So, what do you think?
这下我们再也撞不了衫了
I think we're not wearing the same shirt anymore.
对  瑞秋帮我选的
Yeah. Yeah, Rachel picked it out for me.
她让我相信她
She told me to trust her, and you know what?
真高兴我答应了
I'm glad I did.
一路过来回头率暴高
I turned quite a few heads on my way over here.
老兄  别穿成这样
Dude, I really don't think you should be wearing that.
我明白
I see.
有人怕我抢走了女人的目光
Somebody's afraid of a little competition with the ladies?
看起来好用某人就是个女人了
Looks like someone is the ladies!
你嫉妒  因为你不能把这件扒下来
You're just jealous because you couldn't pull this off.
现在失陪了  我约会去
Yeah. Now if you'll excuse me, I have a date.
看到没  大家都只看我
See? All eyes on me!
不能签
We are not signing those papers.
为啥
Why not?
这样做不对  他们搞错了
It's wrong. They made a mistake.
当我们是别人
They think we're somebody else.
上帝的安排  凡人懂什么
God works in mysterious ways.
别再冒充了
You have got to stop.
但她喜欢我们
But she liked us.
她喜欢的是钱德勒医生
She likes Doctor Chandler
和莫妮卡牧师
and Reverend Monica.
如果你想一下
If you think about it,
我其实满像牧师
I'm kind of like a reverend.
作为主厨  我给饥饿的人和穷人提供食物
I mean, as a chef, I serve God
这不也是为上帝服务
by feeding the hungry and poor.
你们一份小牛排卖34块9毛5
Your veal chop is 34.95!
得了
Come on,
幸福来敲门了
I just-- I think we've been given an opportunity.
不如将错就错
The mistake's already made.
他们已经在写书面报告了
They're writing up the papers now.
但我们不是她要选的人
But we're not the ones she chose.
你竟然理直气壮
How can you feel okay about this?
因为…
Because.
虽然我们不是她选中的人
We may not be who she thinks we are...
但没人会比我们更爱那个小娃娃
...but no one will ever love that baby more than us.
-我明白  -我的意思是
- I know.  - I mean, who knows...
谁知道我们到底还要等多久
...how long it's gonna take for someone else
才会有人再选我们
to give us a baby?
万一永远没人选我们
What if no one ever picks us?
哦  亲爱的
Oh, honey....
求你了
Please?
求你了  我们就快要成功了
Please. We are so close.
莫妮卡  我也想要孩子
Monica, I want a baby too.
但她要送出他的心肝宝贝
But this woman is giving away her child.
她应该知道对方的真实身份
She deserves to know who it's going to.
好吧  你说的没错
Okay. You're right.
我们告诉她真相
So we'll tell the truth.
但是谁知道呢
And who knows, you know?
没准她会因为我们告诉她真相而喜欢我们
Maybe she'll like us for us.
或许她会
Maybe she will.
我怎么就不是牧师呢
Why couldn't I have been a reverend?
你是犹太教的
You're Jewish.
差别不大
Technicality!
女士点的田园沙拉
Garden salad for the lady.
看来很诱人  真会点
Oh, that looks great. Good ordering.
男士点的海鲜拼盘
Seafood platter for the gentleman,
另有一盘薯条
and extra fries.
请慢用
Enjoy.
薯条很美味
Those fries look delicious.
你也喜欢吃法国薯条
I didn't know you liked French fries.
吃吧  我的就是你的
Help yourself. What's mine is yours.
好大的蒸粉蚌
Wow, are those stuffed clams?
对  是我的蒸粉蚌
Yes, they are my stuffed clams.
吃薯条如何
How about those fries, though, huh?
-很好吃  -是啊
- They are delicious.  - Yeah.
你真漂亮  知道吗
You are beautiful, you know that?
嘴真甜
That is so sweet.
好的
Okay, then.
你捣什么乱
Now look what you did!
什么  不怎么了
What? What is the matter with you?
我不喜欢
I don't like it
别人抢我盘子里的东西吃
when people take food off of my plate, okay?
但你说过"我的就是你的"
But you said, "What's mine is yours."
我那是客气
Well, I didn't mean it!
好吧  对不起
Fine. Sorry,
没想到你这么在乎
I didn't think it was that big a deal.
不  我很抱歉
No, I'm sorry. I....
是我反应过激了
I'm overreacting, okay?
在食物方面
It's just, when it comes to food, l...
我有一些戒律
...have certain rules...
我是说
...okay? I mean...
有些事可以做
...there are things you do,
有些事是禁止的
and, you know, things that you don't do.
这儿很不错
Wow, this place looks great.
你会喜欢的
Oh, you are gonna love it.
真高兴我们终于能一起吃饭了
And I'm so glad we're finally doing this.
-我也是  -我来
- Me too.  - Here.
真有趣
So this was fun.
刚才的事真抱歉
I really am sorry about, you know, before.
你一定要知道
And I want to make sure you know
我真的喜欢你
I really do like you.
是啊  但是没有喜欢蛤蚌那么多
Sure, just not as much as clams.
蒸粉蚌
Well, stuffed clams....
女士要的巧克力甜品
Chocolate torte for the lady.
男士的奶酪蛋糕
Cheesecake for the gentleman.
先生
Excuse me, sir.
我的蛋糕好像有些红的乱七八糟的东西
There seems to be some sort of red crap on my cheesecake.
是的  那是覆盆子酱汁
Yes, that's a raspberry coulis.
点奶酪蛋糕真够蠢
I'm so stupid ordering cheesecake,
还想说吃健康食品
trying to be healthy.
哦  不
Oh, no.
工作电话  我得复机
This is work. I should call in.
失陪
Can you excuse me?
当然 请便  没问题
Yeah, sure. No problem.
干嘛
What are you doing?
你不是不和人分享食物
I thought you don't share food?
才没有
Sure I do.
覆盆子酱汁
Coulis?
不  我都不能吃你的蛤蚌
No. If I can't have your clams,
你也不能碰我的甜品
you can't have my dessert.
规则是双向的
This is a two-way street.
是吗
Really?
是的
Really.
我回来时希望它完好无损
Now this all better be here when I come back.
当然  我能控制自己
Yeah, of course. I can control myself.
别再瞪着我
Stop staring at me!
就一小口
Just a tiny little....
我甚至不感觉抱歉
I'm not even sorry.
-嗨   -嗨
- Hi.  - Hey.
领养的初步手续就这些了
So these are the preliminary forms for an open adoption.
有很多东西要看
There's a lot to go over,
但是过的时候我会一一解释
but I'll explain as we go through.
-孩子的照片   -对
- Is that a picture? - Yeah.
是上周给小婴儿拍的B超
It's a sonogram they took of the baby last week.
你们也许有兴趣看看
I thought you might want to see it.
医生快看
Look, doctor.
签字前
Look, before we sign anything,
我们得谈谈
we really have to talk.
我们不是你选中的夫妇
We're not who you think we are.
什么意思
I don't understand.
领养机构肯定出了什么错
The agency must have made a mistake.
我太太不是牧师
My wife is not a reverend,
我不是医生
and I'm not a doctor.
-啊   -不可能
- What? - That's impossible.
如果你愿意  我可以替你开刀
I could perform an operation on you
向你证明
and prove it if you'd like.
我去查档案  失陪
I have to check your file. Excuse me.
你们到底是谁
So who are you?
我们是叫莫妮卡和钱德勒  纽约来的
Our names really are Monica and Chandler. We're from New York.
但重要的是
Yeah, but the important thing to know about us...
我们真的很爱这个小孩
...is how much we would care for this little baby.
你们先前跟我撒谎
So you lied to me before?
我们"犯了伪证罪"
Well, we "bore false witness."
看  我真有当牧师的天赋
See? I could be a reverend.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我们希望说明真相后
But we were hoping that since we told you the truth...
你能网开一面...
...that you still might consider--
把我的宝贝给你们
Giving you my baby?
发生这一切后  你们以为还会给你们
You think I'd give you my child after this?
不必马上决定
You don't have to decide now.
请看看我们的档案
If you look at our file--
没兴趣  到此为止
I don't want to look at your file. This is over.
艾瑞卡  请等等
Erica, wait.
我跟你无话可说
I have nothing to say to you.
你有任何理由生气
Look, you have every reason to be upset.
我们是撒了谎
We did lie.
但那是因为
But only because we've been waiting
我们想要个孩子等太久了
and trying to have a baby for so long.
我们也不知道下一个机会
And we don't know how long it's gonna be
何年何月才会到来
before we get another chance again.
让你的牧师祈祷去吧
Why don't you ask the reverend to pray on it?
艾瑞卡  求你了
Erica, please.
考虑一下我们吧
Just consider us.
找他们要我们的资料
Ask them to see our file.
我们姓宾
Our last name's Bing.
我太太是个主厨  我从事广告业
My wife's a chef, and I'm in advertising.
嗯
Oh, yeah.
我的确喜欢你们
I actually liked you guys.
但已经不重要了
But it doesn't matter.
你们不该撒谎
Because what you did was wrong.
但你喜欢我们对不对
But you did like us.
你也应该喜欢我们
And you should.
我太太是个很了不起的女人
My wife's an incredible woman.
她有爱心  乐于奉献  关怀他人
She is loving, and devoted and caring.
别告诉她我这么说过
And don't tell her I said this,
但她一贯正确
but the woman's always right.
我爱我太太胜过世上一切事物
I love my wife more than anything in this world.
所以...
And it...
不能给她个孩子我难受死了
It kills me that I can't give her a baby.
我很想要个孩子
I really want a kid.
有了孩子以后
And when that day finally comes,
我会学习如何做是个好爸爸
I'll learn how to be a good dad.
但我太太...
But my wife...
她已经是个好妈妈
...she's already there.
她是一个妈妈
She's a mother...
可惜没孩子
...without a baby.
求你了
Please?
你还想要那个孩子吗
You still want that baby?
上帝保佑你  钱德勒·宾
God bless you, Chandler Bing!
原来这件毛衣是女款的
Turns out this sweater is made for a woman.
那你还穿
So why are you still wearing it?
以为很软和
Because it's soft.
今天过得如何
Hey, so how was your date?
不太好
Not so good.
看来今晚就我们两个了
Well, looks like it's just the two of us tonight,
对吧  哥们
huh, buddy?
是啊  你知道吗
Yeah. And you know what?
还有更倒霉的时候呢
We could do a lot worse.
-是阿 -嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
乔伊从不分享食物
Joey doesn't share food!